Hey, could you calm down?
I am calm.
I just don't understand how
he got a perfect score.
It shouldn't even be possible.
Were the questions really that hard?
We're not just talking "hard."
They were far beyond what any
high schooler should be learning!
In other words, they weren't
meant to be solved.
I've been thinking.
You think maybe Ayanokoji's
not on the level?
It's possible!
Maybe he cheated to get
the answers in advance—
Hang on.
There's not a damn bit of evidence
that Ayanokoji did anything wrong.
Don't pin that crap on a guy
when he's not even here.
What's with you, Ken?
You're on Ayanokoji's side now?
It's not about picking sides.
I just think it's more likely that he got
that perfect score under his own power.
But on Ayanokoji's OAA, his Academic
Achievement was even lower than mine.
So maybe he was slacking off
before, like Koenji does.
Let's calm down, everyone.
There's a lot we don't know just yet.
And Sudo-kun, isn't it
time for your practice?
Y-Yeah. Guess it is.
I've gotta get going, too.
Sorry, but could you
stay here with Keisei?
Yeah. See you later, Miyacchi.
Classroom of the Elite 4th Season 2nd Year 1st Term
#5 The Twenty-Million Man
It seems you finished your
talk with the acting chairman.
I suppose.
You've become rather famous.
I'm not pleased about it, but I
considered it a necessary measure.
But how will you explain
this to your classmates?
I'm about to start dealing with it now.
Be prepared for an interrogation.
Hey.
How did you get a perfect score in math?
Not even Ichinose or
Sakayanagi did that well.
You're the only one in the whole year.
Regarding that...
I'll explain.
I was asking Kiyotaka.
True.
But I think I'm the one with
the answer you're seeking.
Do you remember how
Ayanokoji-kun's desk and mine
were next to each other
when we first arrived?
When we were talking, it came up that
he was actually academically gifted.
Hang on. His scores have been average
across the board since he arrived here.
That's because I asked him to hold back.
Why would you do that?
To reserve his talents for
when they were needed.
Call it an ace in the hole, perhaps.
It's hard to believe.
Wouldn't high scores from the start
have been better for the class?
Superlative students will be seen
by other classes as a threat.
They might try to eliminate
him sooner or later.
You thought he'd be putting
a target on his back?
Yes.
And indeed, Ayanokoji-kun was
targeted by Sakayanagi-san
during the class vote test.
Then why did he reveal his skills now?
Over the course of a year,
Class D has become far more united.
We're able to make proper
decisions, as well.
Even if someone were to
target Ayanokoji-kun now,
we would be able to work
together to protect him.
That's why I decided to reveal his
ability and raise up our class baseline.
I understand your strategy.
Is math the only field he's excellent in?
I can't tell you that at this time.
Either way, hiding the truth will
make him a greater thorn in
the other classes' sides.
That makes sense!
I really understand what you're saying.
They won't know how to deal with someone
whose stats they don't fully know.
And if his own classmates don't know,
they can't hit us up for information.
Yes. It's best to convince
them he's an unknown quantity.
I'm sure the other classes will
be reeling from the revelation.
That's the explanation behind
Ayanokoji-kun's perfect score.
I'm sorry for shocking you.
You're just going to leave
without saying a word?
Why didn't you tell us
about what you did today?
You can't trust us, is that it?
I understand why you're angry.
You were all very kind in teaching me.
I'm sorry.
To be honest, I'm still mad about it.
But we've been in the group for a long
time, so there are other things I know.
Like that you're not a bad person.
Thank you, Keisei.
H-How about you shake
hands... and make up?
Yeah, that's a great idea!
There, all friends again!
And to celebrate the reunion,
after Miyacchi's practice is over,
let's meet up at Keyaki Mall!
Ayanokoji-kun!
Meeting someone?
I'm getting dinner with my friends.
I saw your test results.
That was amazing!
Your OAA from last year didn't
suggest you were capable of that.
I discussed it with a classmate and
decided to hide my math skills.
So you were just hiding it before?
You seem to be a more troublesome
opponent than I thought.
Kanzaki-kun, don't talk
about him like that.
It's natural for all the classes
to have their own strategies.
Ayanokoji-kun's not our enemy.
They've already dissolved our alliance.
Class 2-D is unavoidably our enemy.
That's enough, Kanzaki-kun.
Yes, I suppose I've lost my cool.
I'm heading off.
Sorry about that.
He's a little stressed,
under the circumstances.
We've dropped to Class C, you know?
I realize we need to toughen up already...
But...
Do you remember what I said before?
Yeah. To keep going with
my classmates to the end.
Moving forward, you may find some
students don't like how you do things.
They may even betray your class.
No matter what happens,
I hope you keep prioritizing
the trust and protection of
your comrades as you fight.
No worries there.
I'll always protect my classmates.
Even if it happens that someone
in my class has to go away...
I'll make sure I'm the first to go.
I'm relieved to hear that
you're so determined,
but I do have one complaint.
Complaint?
I won't allow you to be expelled.
W-Well... r-right. I'll definitely stay.
W-Well, I've got to go.
Right.
Yesterday was rough, huh?
So it was Suzune's idea for you
to hide that big brain of yours?
Yeah.
Yosuke said that you defended me?
I wouldn't go that far.
I just stated the facts.
Are we keeping your fighting
skills a secret, too?
I don't know what you mean.
Don't play dumb.
You were at least as good
as Hosen back there.
Just how amazing are you, really?
How amazing?
Nah... forget I asked.
It doesn't matter until I
see it for myself anyway.
You're not angry that I didn't tell you?
Well... at first,
I thought it was pretty crazy.
But I'm focused on making
myself better right now.
Doesn't matter to me
what anyone else does.
Oh, I know.
You and Suzune—
We're not dating.
O-Oh. Cool.
Crap, we'd better hurry!
Your smart thinking really helped me out.
Allow me to thank you again.
You certainly owe me one.
We should discuss the 20-million point
reward for having you expelled, though.
It's an absolutely absurd
concept for a special test.
Did the school really approve it?
It's possible someone's put a bounty
on my head to rile up the first-years.
Someone with the ability to pay that much,
or to make the first-years
think they could...
The student council president?
Could President Nagumo have set this up?
I'm not sure. I can't imagine
why he'd hate me that much.
President Nagumo saw
my brother as a rival,
but my brother was only interested in you.
It wouldn't surprise me
if he had complicated feelings
about that, like I did.
I won't say it's a perfect opportunity,
but I'm going to meet
with President Nagumo
and see how he responds to me wanting
to join the student council.
I see.
You wanted me to join the student council
to keep an eye on President Nagumo,
but you want me to do more than
keep an eye on him, don't you?
Your brother cared about
maintaining tradition.
Nagumo is the opposite.
But I'm not judging the
correctness of either approach.
Part of me does want to
see Nagumo's reforms.
If that's all you want, why force
me to join the student council?
If Nagumo does start moving things
in a disadvantageous direction,
we'll need someone to stop him, won't we?
There are parts of this that I don't
like, but it serves my ends, as well.
Well, will you join me?
Join you?
Yes. If President Nagumo is
behind the bounty on your head,
your presence might trigger a reaction.
All right.
Talk to me? Why?
I realize your time is valuable,
so I'll get right to the point.
I would like to join the student council.
That's an unexpected turn of events.
It makes me hesitant to simply say yes.
I thought you'd take all
the help you could get?
You're a special case, Horikita Suzune.
Tell me why you want to join
the student council now.
I've had friction with
my brother in the past.
I joined this school to
try to clear that up.
But even after I came here,
our relationship didn't change.
In the year before he graduated, I never
even had a proper conversation with him.
So you finally made peace?
Yes, at the very end.
And for the first time, I became
curious about the student council,
to which he devoted his student life.
I took the long way getting there,
but I now want to walk the
same road that he did.
The road your brother walked, eh?
So you intend to become student
council president eventually?
Yes. I intend to become
student council president.
I see.
But Honami has been working hard for
a year as a student council executive.
You realize you'll have a
lot of ground to make up?
I don't think that will
be an impossible task.
Horikita—I don't really
want to call you that.
May I call you Suzune?
As you wish.
Honami being my
only executive out of the second-years
has been a bit of a problem.
Welcome to the student council.
I'll work you hard, Suzune.
I expect it.
Show me that you're not
just talk, all right?
I'm Kiriyama, the vice president.
A pleasure.
Will you be joining the student
council as well, Ayanokoji?
I'll pass.
I'm not a student council kind of person.
That's what I thought you'd say.
By the way, we've gotten past the
initial rush of student council work.
I'll be spending more time with the
underclassmen starting in summer.
We'll have a lot of fun
to look forward to.
You're making me coffee?
Where did this come from?
It's harder with your hurt hand, right?
Yeah.
I meant to ask when I saw you,
but you've got a lot
to make up for, y'know?
Where did that come from?
Now that you got that
perfect score in math,
it's even harder to bring up
the fact that we're dating.
I see.
I don't like it.
I feel like people will think I'm
dating you as a status thing.
Is that bad?
I won't go that far, but...
Dating a pretty girl is like a
status thing for boys, isn't it?
It feels absurd to say you
shouldn't pursue that.
Y-You think I'm pretty?
You think that I'd date
someone who wasn't?
I-I think you're really
handsome, too, Kiyotaka...
Wait just a minute.
O-Okay...
Senpai! It's me!
How's your hand?
I got super worried, so I had
to come and check on you!
Won't you be a sweetie and take this off?
It's late. Can we do this tomorrow?
You didn't forget what
you offered in exchange
for me partnering with Sudo-senpai, did you?
Sorry, but my pantry
is bare at the moment.
Aw, no way! Talk about rotten luck...
You're not alone, are you?
What makes you think that?
Because I've been watching.
I've watched Karuizawa-senpai ever
since she got back to the dorms.
You're busted, okay?
So you'd better not try to lie to me.
I've been nice enough to
keep it a secret, too...
But maybe I should spill the beans?
You weren't up to anything, I hope.
O-Of course not!
And why are you here?!
Here I thought you were involved
in illicit romantic dealings...
You know, pervy stuff!
That's forbidden by the rules.
Oh, those rules don't
really mean anything.
You can even buy this stuff at the shops.
A little present from me to you.
Or maybe... an apology?
What do you need to apologize for?
Oh, you!
That wound on your hand...
You know I was part of that, right?
I was working with Hosen-kun.
She was?
Ayanokoji-senpai, I think you might
have the wrong idea about me.
The wrong idea?
I'm not your enemy.
That seems hard to believe.
Why is that?
Because I filled Hosen-kun with
ideas about how to get you expelled?
W-Wait a minute!
What do you mean, you tried
to get him expelled?!
Oh, you haven't told your girlfriend, huh?
What about the 20-million point bounty?
The 20-million what?
You should ask your boyfriend
to fill you in later.
Right, Senpai?
You learned about the plan when
we went shopping together.
Because I was so confident
in picking out the knife...
Right?
You're saying you set that
up so that I would realize?
That's very kind of you.
I didn't want you expelled for the bounty
without giving you a fighting chance.
That would just be mean.
Her mind moves at incredible speeds.
She certainly could be
the White Room student.
But what would it benefit her
to reveal her true nature?
Well, I've made my apology,
so I guess I'll get going.
Use these groceries however you'd like!
What in the world?!
Oh, you want me to stay?
A-Actually... I'd rather you didn't.
I'll just be going, then!
We haven't had another test since
the one at the end of April.
I haven't noticed any attempts by the
White Room student to target me, either.
Good morning, Ayanokoji-senpai.
Hey. Morning.
Is there something up there?
No.
I was just gazing at the blue sky.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Yes, I'm sorry about that.
I felt bad about what I put you through.
Do you resent me?
I see no reason to resent you.
You had a special test to
have me expelled, right?
Is the test over now?
No, it's still on.
It lasts until the second term starts.
Are you curious about why neither
Hosen-kun nor I have come after you?
I would be lying if I said I wasn't.
The last incident made me
realize it would be impossible
to take you out with a plan
based on our day-to-day lives.
So you're waiting for a special test
that involves inter-year interaction?
I hear there was a first-year who
got expelled over the special test.
Yes. A boy was expelled from Class 1-C.
A friend from this school I was
laughing with until yesterday...
Gone, just like that.
It's made me realize anew how important
it is to take nothing for granted.
I intend to live a school
life I won't regret.
Ayanokoji-senpai...
I hope you can live a school
life without regret, as well.
I'm glad to see you all here.
I'm going to explain about
our upcoming summer vacation.
For eight days and seven nights,
you'll be able to enjoy summer
vacation on this luxury liner.
No special tests will occur on the ship.
However, in order to enjoy the trip,
you will need to survive
the next special test.
When does the special test start?
Normally, it would be any day now,
but this particular special test
will take place over summer break.
You'll compete in a deserted
island survival game.